Guide to the Norman E. Thomas Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Biographical Documentation, Series VII
  - Professional Associations
    - Association of Theological Schools (ATS): Committee on Internationalization of Theological Education: CITE Newsletter, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 634)
    - ATS-CITE Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 70, Folder 635)
    - ATS-CITE Minutes, 1981-1985 (Box 70, Folder 636)
    - ATS-CITE Reports, 1981-1985 (Box 70, Folder 637)
    - ATS-CITE Papers (Box 70, Folder 638)
    - International Association for Mission Studies (IAMS): Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 639)
    - IAMS: Conference (4th, Maryknoll, NY, USA) Papers, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 640)
    - IAMS: Conference (5th, Bangalore, India): Papers, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 641)
    - IAMS: Conference (6th, Harare, Zimbabwe): Papers, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 642)
    - IAMS: Conference(7th, Rome, Italy): Papers, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 643)
    - IAMS: Conference Rome: DAB Group Meetings, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 644)
    - IAMS: Conference (8th, Hawaii, USA) Papers, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 645)
    - IAMS: Documentation, Archives, and Bibliography (DAB): Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 646)
    - IAMS/DAB: Minutes/Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 72, Folder 647)
    - IAMS/DAB: Papers on Common International Thesaurus, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 648)
    - IAMS: Newsletter, 1980-1983 (Box 72, Folder 649)
    - Midwest Professors of Mission: Papers, 1987-2001 (Box 72, Folder 650)
    - North American Academy of Ecumenists (NAAE), 1984-1985 (Box 73, Folder 651)
    - Society for the Scientific Study of Religion (SSSR): Annual Meetings (Box 73, Folder 652)
    - Society of Christian Ethics (SCE): Annual Meetings (Box 73, Folder 654)
  - Sermons
    - Portland, 1957-1959 (Box 73, Folder 659-661)
    - Boston, 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 662)
    - Southern Rhodesia, 1962-1972 (Box 73, Folder 663)
    - United States, 1969, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 664)
    - Zambia, 1973-1976 (Box 74, Folder 665)
    - New England, 1976-1983 (Box 74, Folder 666)
  - Talks
    - Evangelization and Church Renewal (Box 74, Folder 669)
    - Mission Interpretation (Box 74, Folder 670)
    - Social and Ethical Issues (Box 74, Folder 671)
  - Travel and Travel-Study Seminars
    - Mexico/Caribbean, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 672)
    - Australia/Southeast Asia (Malaysia/Singapore, Philippines, Thailand), 1980 (Box 74, Folder 673)
    - Mexico/Caribbean, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 674)
    - Africa (Zimbabwe)/ India, 1981/1982 (Box 74, Folder 675)
    - Southern Africa (South Africa/Zimbabwe), 1983 (Box 74, Folder 676)
    - Israel, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 677)
    - India (Fulbright Program), 1984 (Box 75, Folder 678)
    - Africa(Zimbabwe), 1984/1985 (Box 75, Folder 679)
    - Africa (Kenya/Zimbabwe), 1986 (Box 75, Folder 680)
    - China, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 681)
    - South America (Chile, Argentina, Uruguay), 1987 (Box 75, Folder 682)
    - Southern Africa (Zimbabwe, South Africa), 1991 (Box 76, Folder 683)
    - Zimbabwe (WCC Harare Assembly), 1998 (Box 76, Folder 684)
  - Writing
    - Proposals (Box 76, Folder 685)
  - Other Personal Material / Addendum
    - Lecturer and Dean, Epworth T.C., 1968-1972 (Box 76, Folder 686)
    - Urban Evangelism Sec. CCR, 1967-1970 (Box 76, Folder 687)
    - New Religious Movements (Box 76, Folder 688)
    - Research Projects (Box 76, Folder 689)
    - Missionary Board of Missions (Box 76, Folder 690)
    - Ordained, Rhodesia Conference (Box 77, Folder 691)
    - Dean, Mindolo Ecumentical Foundation (Box 77, Folder 692)
    - Latin America (Box 77, Folder 693)
    - Asian Theology (Box 77, Folder 694)
    - African Theology (Box 77, Folder 695)
    - UTS (Box 77, Folder 696)
    - Ethiopia (Box 77, Folder 697)
    - Kenya (Box 78, Folder 698)
    - Tanzania (Box 78, Folder 699)
    - Zambia (Box 78, Folder 700)
    - Orthodox (Box 78, Folder 701)